I'm going to show you how to make a seafarer's double.
I just wanted to talk a little bit about salmon.
Salmon is so popular throughout the world and certainly in the United States.
Lots of people eat it every single day and the best kind of salmon is a Pacific northwest salmon.
This happens to be Atlantic salmon.
Let me talk about the Pacific salmon for a minute.
It is the most prized of all the salmon in the world, it's the best, the freshest, the most delicious and whenever you can get wild seafood of any kind, do that as opposed to farm and seafood.
Salmon is really interesting that they live in both freshwater and saltwater.
They go to freshwater to breed and after they breed, they die.
Atlantic salmon actually don't die after they breed and this is an example like I said of Atlantic salmon, but unfortunately Atlantic salmon are very scarce.
You're not going to find wild Atlantic salmon anywhere so the most of the Atlantic salmon you get will be farmed.
It's farmed in Norway, United States, Chile lots of different places but if you can like I said try to get the wild salmon.
In our next clip we're going to prep our salmon for grilling.